Learning CapCut day 277.
Today we will learn how [music] to
create this type of heart shape
transition and that too in very simple
steps.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Bring the image down. Adjust its
duration.
Go to [music] mask and select
horizontal. Add a key frame at the
starting point and move it up. Then add
[music] another key frame and move it
down. Apply the flow two graph.
Add two key frames. [music] Go to the
starting key frame and zoom in. Apply
the flow two graph.
Go to animation and select cross shape.
Set its duration to [music] 0.4 seconds.
Go to effects and select oblique blur.
Adjust it from 100% [music]
to 0%. Then go to effects again and
select shake.
Adjust it to [music] 40%, 60%, 0%.
Thanks for watching.